<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>It is All about FrontEnd</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on It is All about FrontEnd</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 10:56:15 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to disable `eval()` in your website</title>
      <link>/posts/xixi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 10:56:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/xixi/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nextjs API: The Complete Guide in 2023(for Pages Router)</title>
      <link>/posts/nextjs-api-the-complete-guide-in-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 12:15:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/nextjs-api-the-complete-guide-in-2023/</guid>
      <description>Rendering pre-renders:
By default, Next.js pre-renders every page. Pre-rendering can result in better performance.
Nextjs Supports one or several rendering modes at the same time:
In Server-side Rendering (SSR) mode,the page HTML is generated on each request.
In Static Site Generation (SSG) mode,the page HTML is generated at build time.
In Client-side Rendering (CSR) mode,the page HTML is generated at client side by javascript.
routing Link: Do route transitions on clientside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Front End Developer Roadmap 2024: Mastering the Evolving Landscape</title>
      <link>/posts/roadmap-dev-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 20:14:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/roadmap-dev-2024/</guid>
      <description>Greetings fellow developers! As we step into 2024, the frontend development landscape continues to evolve at a rapid pace. With over a decade of experience in the field, I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share a comprehensive roadmap to guide you through the challenges and opportunities that lie ahead. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned developer or just starting your journey, this roadmap is designed to equip you for success in the dynamic world of frontend development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Highest Paying Industries For Ordinary People In the next 10 years</title>
      <link>/posts/next-10-years-make-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 10:05:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/next-10-years-make-money/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to the industries with the most money-making opportunities, many people will think of the real estate, finance, and IT industries, and they did before.
People who were engaged in real estate in the early days only needed to buy with their eyes closed, and then resell or rent it out. They could make money while lying down, making money passively.
Later, coincident with the rapid development of the financial industry, the financial industry became popular, and wealthy families would do everything possible to make their children Go study in finance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make popular YouTube videos with the help of AI tools</title>
      <link>/posts/make-popular-youtube-videos-with-the-help-of-ai-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 22:10:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/make-popular-youtube-videos-with-the-help-of-ai-tools/</guid>
      <description>As a web developer, creating and operating your own YouTube channel can not only share knowledge and promote personal brand building, but also play a role in career development. Currently, AI technology is developing rapidly. This article will tell you how to use the power of AI to create videos.
Channel Research Find some content on the platform that is related to your positioning. The number of fans and views are very good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12 Passive Income for Web Developers [2023]</title>
      <link>/posts/passive-income-for-webdev/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 10:42:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/passive-income-for-webdev/</guid>
      <description>As a person seeking to earn passive income, you know it is a long-term decision requiring short-term trade-offs. If you are willing to invest your time, skills, and money towards achieving this goal, the potential to generate substantial income in the long run, is immense.
As a web developer, you are lucky because the technology-driven world heavily relies on your expertise. Small and large businesses alike require web development services to operate effectively, making this profession an ideal source of passive income.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Best Practices for Writing Clean React Code</title>
      <link>/posts/writing-clean-react-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 10:25:26 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/writing-clean-react-code/</guid>
      <description>Writing clean React code is important because it reflects a careful and dedicated mindset. When we take the time to write clean, well-organized code, we are demonstrating a commitment to the craft of software development. Clean code proves that we value the quality of our work and are willing to invest the time and effort required to produce something truly exceptional.
Why is organizing and writing clean React Code important? Clean code organization is important in React for practical reasons, as well as for its visual impact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to fix CORS error &#34;No &#39;Access-Control-Allow-Origin&#39; header is present on the requested resource&#34;？</title>
      <link>/posts/fix-cors-error/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 09:00:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/fix-cors-error/</guid>
      <description>There are several online apps available nowadays. The majority of systems now offer some form of online user interface. These interfaces deal with the client-side presentation or how to display it to the user. The user can interact with the web apps and request information or updates from the server. The data gets saved in a database that the server may access. The client-side web application requests information from the web server, which the server responds with by retrieving it from the database.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>React version 18: new features and updates</title>
      <link>/posts/react-version-18-new-features-and-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 14:53:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/react-version-18-new-features-and-updates/</guid>
      <description>React has come a long way in the past decade, undergoing significant transformations that have made it one of the most widely used front-end UI frameworks available today.
Initially, React’s verbose syntax made it challenging for developers to work with. However, React introduced the JSX syntax, simplifying the creation of components. To follow, functional components with Hooks made it easier to handle state and life-cycle functions, leading to more elegant, readable, and maintainable code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How can beginners learn to use hugo quickly and effectively?</title>
      <link>/posts/how-can-beginners-learn-to-use-hugo-quickly-and-effectively/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 19:41:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/how-can-beginners-learn-to-use-hugo-quickly-and-effectively/</guid>
      <description>Hugo is a static website generator written in Go language, which can help you quickly build concise and efficient static websites. For beginners, here are some suggestions to help you learn to develop websites with Hugo quickly and effectively:
Understand and install Hugo First read the official Hugo documentation to understand the basic concepts of Hugo, including content organization, templates, themes, etc.
Then, depending on your operating system, download the latest version of Hugo from the Hugo GitHub Release page.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
